<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NPC on Terminal</title>
    <link>/tags/npc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NPC on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/npc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alora</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/alora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/alora/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lady of Winter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Alora]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbiter</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/arbiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/arbiter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/arbiter-headshot2.webp&#34; alt=&#34;arbiter-headshot2.webp&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/arbiter-warrior.png&#34; alt=&#34;arbiter-warrior.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Angel of Justice&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Serves the dusk lord&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Marked the party with her symbol&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;restoring-the-crystal-at-the-leyline-barrier&#34;&gt;Restoring the crystal at the leyline barrier&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To restore the crystal within the arcane circle at the Summer Leyline Temple, the issue lies likely not with the crystal alone but with the disturbance in the leyline energy and the balance of the arcane circle itself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consider these steps to reattune the crystal and restore the barrier’s integrity:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elara Sunforge</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/elara-sunforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/elara-sunforge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/elara-sunforge.png&#34; alt=&#34;elara-sunforge.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Name&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name:&lt;/strong&gt; Elara Sunforge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Master Smith of the [[Summer Court]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Race:&lt;/strong&gt; Summer Eladrin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Age:&lt;/strong&gt; Ageless, but appears to be in her late 20s&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role:&lt;/strong&gt; Renowned as the most skilled smith in the Summer Court, Elara has the knowledge and ability to reforge the legendary blade, Summer&amp;rsquo;s Edge.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;physical-appearance&#34;&gt;Physical Appearance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hair:&lt;/strong&gt; Elara has a stylish pixie cut hairstyle, her hair a vibrant golden color that seems to shimmer like sunlight. The short, sleek cut gives her an air of efficiency and modernity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eyes:&lt;/strong&gt; Her eyes are a bright emerald green, sparkling with intelligence and a hint of mischief. They reflect the warmth and intensity of the summer sun.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skin:&lt;/strong&gt; Her skin has a warm, sun-kissed glow, smooth and flawless, exuding vitality and health.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build:&lt;/strong&gt; Elara is lean and athletic, with toned muscles that speak to her physical strength and skill as a smith. She moves with grace and confidence.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attire:&lt;/strong&gt; She wears a sleeveless tunic made of lightweight, flame-resistant materials, adorned with intricate golden patterns. Her blacksmith&amp;rsquo;s apron is made of enchanted leather, and she often has a pair of protective goggles perched on her head. Her outfit is both practical and stylish, fitting for a master smith of her stature.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;personality&#34;&gt;Personality&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confident and Skilled:&lt;/strong&gt; Elara is highly confident in her abilities, and her reputation as a master smith is well-deserved. She takes great pride in her work and is always striving for perfection.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Warm and Approachable:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite her formidable skills, Elara is warm and approachable. She enjoys sharing her knowledge and is always willing to teach or offer advice to those who seek it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Spirit:&lt;/strong&gt; As a member of the Summer Court, Elara has a competitive spirit and loves participating in and watching the games and contests of skill held in the coliseum. She believes that friendly competition brings out the best in everyone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;role-playing-tips&#34;&gt;Role-Playing Tips&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confident Speech:&lt;/strong&gt; When portraying Elara, speak with confidence and enthusiasm. She is passionate about her craft and proud of her abilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Warmth and Humor:&lt;/strong&gt; Elara has a warm, friendly demeanor and a good sense of humor. She enjoys banter and is quick to laugh, making those around her feel at ease.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attention to Detail:&lt;/strong&gt; Elara is meticulous and detail-oriented, often examining items or situations with a critical eye. She appreciates quality and craftsmanship in all things.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-dialogue&#34;&gt;Example Dialogue&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Reforging Summer&amp;rsquo;s Edge:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Ah, Summer&amp;rsquo;s Edge! A blade of such legend and power. To reforge it would be an honor and a challenge I eagerly accept. This sword was crafted to protect our realm, and it will do so again.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the Summer Court:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Welcome to the Summer Court, where the sun never sets on our spirit of competition and excellence. Here, we celebrate strength, skill, and the joy of creation.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the Coliseum:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;The coliseum is the heart of our court, a place where champions are made and legends are born. There is no greater thrill than the roar of the crowd and the heat of the forge.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;setting-the-summer-court&#34;&gt;Setting: The Summer Court&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture:&lt;/strong&gt; The Summer Court is styled like ancient Rome, with grand marble buildings, open courtyards, and majestic columns. The streets are bustling with activity, and the air is filled with the sounds of laughter, music, and the clang of metal from the forges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farkris</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/farkris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/farkris/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/farkris.png&#34; alt=&#34;farkris.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name:&lt;/strong&gt; Lord Thalorin, the Lord of Autumn&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Race:&lt;/strong&gt; Autumn Eladrin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Age:&lt;/strong&gt; Centuries old, with the wisdom and experience of many lifetimes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Lord of the Autumn Court&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reputation:&lt;/strong&gt; Renowned as a legendary diplomat and negotiator, respected by allies and adversaries alike&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;physical-appearance&#34;&gt;Physical Appearance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Features:&lt;/strong&gt; Lord Thalorin has sharp, angular features that exude both wisdom and authority. His eyes are a deep, warm amber, reflecting the golden hues of autumn leaves. His gaze is piercing yet compassionate, capable of discerning truth and intention.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hair:&lt;/strong&gt; His hair is long and flowing, a rich auburn color that shimmers with golden highlights, reminiscent of autumn foliage. It is often worn loose or elegantly braided.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attire:&lt;/strong&gt; Thalorin dresses in robes of deep red, gold, and brown, the colors of the autumn season. His clothing is finely crafted, adorned with intricate patterns of leaves and vines. A cloak of autumn leaves drapes over his shoulders, enchanted to shift colors with the changing light.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accessories:&lt;/strong&gt; He wears a circlet of intertwined branches and leaves, signifying his status as the Lord of Autumn. A pendant shaped like a golden leaf hangs around his neck, an ancient artifact of the Autumn Court.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;personality&#34;&gt;Personality&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diplomatic and Wise:&lt;/strong&gt; Thalorin is a master of words and persuasion, always seeking peaceful resolutions and understanding. He speaks with eloquence and thoughtfulness, considering the perspectives of all parties involved.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calm and Compassionate:&lt;/strong&gt; He exudes a sense of calm and patience, even in the face of conflict. His compassion for all living beings is evident in his actions and decisions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resilient and Determined:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite his gentle demeanor, Thalorin possesses a steely resolve. He has faced countless challenges and remains steadfast in his duty to protect the Autumn Court and its allies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legendary Diplomat:&lt;/strong&gt; Thalorin&amp;rsquo;s skills in diplomacy and negotiation are unmatched. He can defuse tense situations and forge alliances even in the most dire circumstances.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fey Magic:&lt;/strong&gt; As an Eladrin, Thalorin has innate magical abilities tied to the seasons. He can cast spells related to nature, enchantment, and illusion, often using them to create peaceful and harmonious environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ancient Wisdom:&lt;/strong&gt; Having lived for centuries, Thalorin possesses a vast knowledge of history, lore, and arcane secrets. His advice and insights are invaluable to those who seek his counsel.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;role-playing-tips&#34;&gt;Role-Playing Tips&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eloquent Speech:&lt;/strong&gt; When portraying Thalorin, use formal and eloquent language. His words should flow smoothly, with a cadence that commands attention and respect. He chooses his words carefully, always aiming to convey wisdom and understanding.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calm Demeanor:&lt;/strong&gt; Thalorin&amp;rsquo;s presence is calming and reassuring. He remains composed even in the face of anger or hostility, defusing tensions with his serene and patient demeanor.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empathy and Compassion:&lt;/strong&gt; Thalorin listens intently to others, showing genuine interest in their concerns and perspectives. He offers compassionate advice and seeks solutions that benefit all parties.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steely Resolve:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite his gentle nature, Thalorin is unwavering in his convictions. When necessary, he can be firm and resolute, standing his ground and making difficult decisions for the greater good.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Historical References:&lt;/strong&gt; Thalorin often references past events and ancient wisdom in his conversations, drawing on his vast experience to provide context and insight. This reinforces his age and the depth of his knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-dialogue&#34;&gt;Example Dialogue&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Diplomacy:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;In every heart, there lies the seed of understanding. It is through patience and empathy that we nurture this seed, allowing it to bloom into peace.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Conflict:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;The shadow dragon is a creature of chaos, yet even in darkness, there is a sliver of light. We must seek this light, for it is our only hope against the encroaching night.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On History:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I have witnessed the rise and fall of empires, the ebb and flow of time. In every era, it is the bonds we forge and the wisdom we share that endure.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By embodying these traits and following these role-playing tips, you can bring Lord Thalorin to life as a memorable and influential NPC in your campaign. His presence and guidance will add depth and gravitas to the story, providing the party with a powerful ally in their quest.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis, the Flameskull</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/francis-the-flameskull/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/francis-the-flameskull/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tiny undead&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Armor Class&lt;/strong&gt; 13&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hit Points&lt;/strong&gt; 40 (9d4 + 18)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt; 0 ft., fly 40 ft. (hover)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;STR&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;DEX&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;CON&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;INT&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;WIS&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;CHA&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;-5 (+1)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;+3 (+1)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;+2 (+1)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;+3 (+1)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;+0 (+1)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;+0 (+1)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills&lt;/strong&gt; Arcana +7, Perception +2&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Damage Resistances&lt;/strong&gt; Lightning, Necrotic, Piercing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Damage Immunities&lt;/strong&gt; Cold, Fire, Poison&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Condition Immunities&lt;/strong&gt; Charmed, Frightened, Paralyzed, Poisoned, Prone&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senses&lt;/strong&gt; Darkvision 60 ft., passive Perception 12&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Languages&lt;/strong&gt; Common&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proficiency Bonus&lt;/strong&gt; +2&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;actions&#34;&gt;Actions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multiattack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; The flameskull uses Fire Ray twice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fire Ray.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Ranged Spell Attack: +5 to hit, range 30 ft., one target. Hit: 10 (3d6) fire damage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;special-abilities&#34;&gt;Special Abilities&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Illumination.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; The flameskull sheds either dim light in a 15-foot radius, or bright light in a 15-foot radius and dim light for an additional 15 feet. It can switch between the options as an action.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magic Resistance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; The flameskull has advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rejuvenation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; If the flameskull is destroyed, it regains all its hit points in 1 hour unless holy water is sprinkled on its remains or a Dispel Magic or Remove Curse spell is cast on them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spellcasting.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; The flameskull is a 5th-level spellcaster. Its spellcasting ability is Intelligence (spell save DC 13, +5 to hit with spell attacks). It requires no somatic or material components to cast its spells. The flameskull has the following wizard spells prepared:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cantrip (at will): mage hand&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1st level (3 slots): magic missile, shield&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2nd level (2 slots): blur, flaming sphere&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3rd level (1 slot): fireball&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;spells&#34;&gt;Spells&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;magic-missile&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magic Missile&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;1st-level evocation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hencelle</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/hencelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/hencelle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/hencelle.png&#34; alt=&#34;hencelle.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Earth Genasi, former monk&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tavern keeper at the Aki Matsuri (Fall Festival in Japanese&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Master of Feasts - chief orgaznier of the festivals&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lerissa</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/lerissa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/lerissa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Lerissa.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Lerissa.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;tiefling bartender of the [[Raven’s Perch Tavern]] in Tannis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Former beast master ranger&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knows the local geography&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pet gray wolf, The Dutchess&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serra Flamekissed</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/serra-flamekissed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/serra-flamekissed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/serra-flamekissed.png&#34; alt=&#34;serra-flamekissed.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bartender of the Ember&amp;rsquo;s Embrace in the summer court&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trius</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/trius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/trius/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/trius-portrait.png&#34; alt=&#34;trius-portrait.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/trius-horseback.png&#34; alt=&#34;trius-horseback.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Princess of the winter Court&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Oath of ancients paladin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wielder of a moon blade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Daughter of Alora&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vidrir</title>
      <link>/characters/allies/vidrir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/characters/allies/vidrir/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Druid.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Druid.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Local loremaster that lives in a grove in the Shimmerwood&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Vidrir’s Grove]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Loves [[Lerissa]] ‘s beer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Has some magical talent, including some divination&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in the history of the local area and beyond&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
