<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Factions on Tempus Campaign</title><link>/06---factions/</link><description>Recent content in Factions on Tempus Campaign</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/06---factions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chained Library (2)</title><link>/06---factions/chained-library/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/06---factions/chained-library/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="background">Background&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The Chained Library is a new location with creatures, magic items, and stories. &amp;ldquo;If a little knowledge is a dangerous thing, the Chained Library is a cataclysm lying in wait,&amp;rdquo; says Indratha Nevarre, an antiquarian and sage.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="library-description">Library Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Chained Library is a great fortress built into the black rock cliffs far from civilization. Spellbooks of liches and necromancers and ancient tomes of infernal secrets line the library’s prison-shelves, guarded by blind celestials. The library predates every known kingdom and even some of the younger gods.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Massa’Ista</title><link>/06---factions/massaista/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/06---factions/massaista/</guid><description>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Information guild&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Name translates to “Shared Knowledge” in an odd Elvish dialect&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Based in Hunter’s Hollow - closest large city to Tannis&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Run by “The Fountain” (as in fountain of knowledge
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>No one is allowed to directly meet the Fountain&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The fountain is secretly an elder Oblex&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Emblem is a skull with the floating above the rest of the skull&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Can obtain just about any information for a price&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Knows how to contact agent of the [[Chained Library|Chained Library]] or how to find it&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Bartender of the Iron Eagle tavern in Hunter’s Hollow can provide the password to enter the museum that’s used as a front for the Massa’Ista’s guild house&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>