<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Items on Tempus Campaign</title><link>/04---items/</link><description>Recent content in Items on Tempus Campaign</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/04---items/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summer's Edge</title><link>/04---items/summers-edge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/summers-edge/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>The Blade of Dawning Light&lt;/em>&lt;br>
&lt;em>Weapon (longsword), rare (requires attunement by a good-aligned creature)&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>[!tip] Legends Speak&amp;hellip;
&lt;em>“As long as Summer’s Edge shines, the night shall never truly fall.”&lt;/em>&lt;br>
&lt;em>— Inscription on the sword’s original scabbard&lt;/em>&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Forged in ages past by the smiths of the Summer Court, Summer’s Edge was once the blade of Sir Eirik, Champion of the Summer Court and Captain of the Order of Seasons. It gleamed with the light of the midday sun and cut down countless horrors in the battle against the undead. Though broken during the final stand at the Gates of Season’s End, the blade has been reforged—and its light is rising once again.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Weaver's Journal</title><link>/04---items/weavers-journal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/weavers-journal/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>[!quote] First Sparks
Today, I cast an illusion no one could see through. Father called it child&amp;rsquo;s play — a trick for fairs and fools. But when I showed him the wolf at the window and watched the blood drain from his face, I knew: there is power in belief.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Even without substance, fear is real.&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>[!quote] The Dance of Triggers
Why rely on an audience’s gaze? Why perform for them when I can weave cause and effect into the very fabric of a place? I have found a method to bind illusions to events — a sound, a footstep, a heartbeat. They spring to life when I command them, like faithful servants awaiting their cue. I call it a &amp;ldquo;programmed illusion.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Arcanroot Tobacco Pipe</title><link>/04---items/arcanroot-tobacco-pipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/arcanroot-tobacco-pipe/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="arcanroot-tobacco-pipe">Arcanroot Tobacco Pipe&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Wondrous item, uncommon&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This pipe comes with a pouch containing 27 (5d10) pinches of arcanroot tobacco.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As an action, you can consume one pinch to pack it into the pipe.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a bonus action, you can light the pipe and blow the smoke onto a solid surface or object.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The smoke forms into a 1-foot diameter ring out to a range of 30 feet, which lasts 5 minutes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bag of Starlight</title><link>/04---items/bag-of-starlight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/bag-of-starlight/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Wondrous item, uncommon&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This inky-dark bag glimmers softly in daylight and shines like a star in darkness, shedding dim light in a 10-foot radius. Inside the bag is complete darkness. The bag has 3 charges, and regains all spent charges daily at dawn.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As an action, you can expend 1 charge to reach inside and catch a handful of starlight like sand. This starlight can be used in either of the following ways:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dagger of Darkness</title><link>/04---items/dagger-of-darkness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/dagger-of-darkness/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Weapon (dagger), rare&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can use an action to cause a necrotic aura to coat the blade. The aura remains for 1 minute or until an attack using this weapon hits a creature. That creature must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or take 2d10 necrotic damage. The dagger can&amp;rsquo;t be used this way again until the next dawn.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Figurine of Wondrous Power (Onyx Dog)</title><link>/04---items/figurine-of-wondrous-power-onyx-dog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/figurine-of-wondrous-power-onyx-dog/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Wondrous Item, rare&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A &lt;strong>figurine of wondrous power&lt;/strong> is a statuette of a beast small enough to fit in a pocket. If you use an action to speak the command word and throw the figurine to a point on the ground within 60 feet of you, the figurine becomes a living creature. If the space where the creature would appear is occupied by other creatures or objects, or if there isn&amp;rsquo;t enough space for the creature, the figurine doesn&amp;rsquo;t become a creature.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Iron bands of binding</title><link>/04---items/iron-bands-of-binding/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/iron-bands-of-binding/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Wondrous Item, rare&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This rusty iron sphere measures 3 inches in diameter and weighs 1 pound. You can use an action to speak the command word and throw the sphere at a Huge or smaller creature you can see within 60 feet of you. As the sphere moves through the air, it opens into a tangle of metal bands.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Make a ranged attack roll with an attack bonus equal to your Dexterity modifier plus your proficiency bonus. On a hit, the target is &lt;a href="https://www.dndbeyond.com/compendium/rules/basic-rules/appendix-a-conditions#Restrained">&lt;strong>restrained&lt;/strong>&lt;/a> until you take a bonus action to speak the command word again to release it. Doing so, or missing with the attack, causes the bands to contract and become a sphere once more.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Serenity’s Journal</title><link>/04---items/serenitys-journal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/serenitys-journal/</guid><description>&lt;p>“I&amp;rsquo;ve never encountered a creature of such sorrow and powerful longing. If only I could share the depth of his darkness with the realm…”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“I can&amp;rsquo;t be the only one to have been engaged by the beauty of his darkness. I must find someone who understands my experiences.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“the dusk lord?!? What a joke. His suffering would surely please the great shadow… would it not?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“I knew it! My lord’s hatred for the ‘god’ runs deep. I must find a way to make them suffer. The curse the Weaver taught me would be perfect!!! Time to gather my supplies. Now… what face to wear when I go to town? The artist? The beggar? The warrior? No…the singer would be just the thing!  She always gets attention and I feel like showing off a bit”&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Summer’s Edge (orig)</title><link>/04---items/summers-edge-orig/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/summers-edge-orig/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="/images/summers-edge-final.png" alt="summers-edge-final.png">&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="background">Background&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Summer&amp;rsquo;s Edge is an ancient elven sword passed down through generations of the noble and prestigious order of knights known as the Guardians of the Summer Court. The sword was crafted by the finest elven blacksmiths and enchanted by powerful elven mages during a time when the spread of the undead threatened the Summer Court.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The sword&amp;rsquo;s first owner was a legendary elven knight, Eirik of the Summer Court, who led the charge against the undead hordes that threatened the safety of the Summer Court. Eirik was a skilled swordsman and a devoted protector of his people. With the help of Summer&amp;rsquo;s Edge, he and his fellow knights were able to successfully repel the undead invasion and restore peace to the Summer Court.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Xolthos note</title><link>/04---items/xolthos-note/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/04---items/xolthos-note/</guid><description>&lt;p>Xolthos,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our progress is swift, but vigilance is essential. The Shadow Dragon&amp;rsquo;s freedom hinges on the weakening of the barrier. We must secure the leyline temples where the barrier is anchored.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Winter Court&amp;rsquo;s crystal has already been damaged. The next target lies within the territory of the Summer Court, where the master smiths reside. Disrupt their leyline crystal, and our victory draws closer.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ensure the elimination of any who might interfere, particularly those who bear the marks of the Dusk Lord. Their resolve must be shattered.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>